arthsalutions.com 2012-09-11

# Privacy Policy- Arth Salutions

**Arth Salutions Privacy Policy**  
The following describes the overall company Privacy Policy of Arth Salutions (referred to as “Arth Salutions”, “we”, “us” and “our”). We understand how important it is to keep your personal information confidential, especially online. Our commitment to protecting your privacy is mentioned in the policies below. This Privacy Policy was created to inform you what information we collect when you visit ArthSalutions.com as well as our customer’s (referred to as “Advertisers”) websites; and then how that information is collected and used by companies that display advertisements(referred to as “Partners”). Those who visit our Advertisers’ websites are referred to as “Prospects” throughout this policy. Because our Privacy Policy may be updated periodically, we encourage you to review these pages on a regular basis.

**Personal and Non-Personal Information**  
Personally Identifiable Information (“PII”) is data about you that is personally identifiable; like your name, email address, credit card number or any other information that is not otherwise publicly available. The PII that Arth Salutions collects from you is information you supply to us; such as your name, email address, credit card number. 

Non-Personally Identifiable Information (“NPII”) data is collected by Arth Salutions and Arth Salutions’s Partners, and is used by Arth Salutions for the purpose of online Retargeting. NPII data collected by Arth Salutions for advertising purposes is completely anonymous, and only includes information such as the Prospect’s IP address, date and time of visit, domain type, and their activity on our Advertiser’s and Partner’s websites. None of this information, individually or grouped together, can be traced back to a specific individual.

**Purpose of collecting information from you**  
We use your personal information to get in touch with you when necessary or to provide the services requested by you. We sometimes use this information internally to direct our efforts for product improvement or contact you as a survey respondent. Please be informed that by giving us this information, you are giving us permission to share such information with any other third party service providers and be contacted by them to provide products or services you’ve requested. We will send information about you to other companies or people only when we need to share your information to provide the product or service you have requested to enable them to contact you or we have your consent from you to share the information. 

We need to share your information with certain service partners in order to respond to your queries / comments or to resolve service issues and to serve you better.

We use the contact information that you have provide to offer you details of products, programs or services that we believe may be of interest to you, including but not limited to newsletters from Arth Salutions. You can easily opt out of a newsletter by clicking the unsubscribe link at the bottom of the e-mail. We do not share, sell, rent or trade personally identifiable information with third parties for their promotional purposes, unless you authorize us to do so. If you’d like to find out more about this or if you have any questions about how we handle personal information generally, please read our full privacy policy. 

**Cookies**  
In computer language, a cookie is used to store data on a computer’s hard drive. Almost all websites utilize cookies to one extent or another. Arth Salutions uses it’s cookies to provide a service known as Retargeting (details explaining Retargeting found below.) A Prospect receives a cookie from Arth Salutions and Arth Salutions’s Partners when they visit ArthSalutions.com, and / or when they visit one of Arth Salutions’s Advertiser’s websites. Arth Salutions has no access to or control over Partner cookies but requires that each Partner only collect NPII information for the use of serving retargeted ads. Any Partner found in violation of this policy will immediately be removed.

**Arth Salutions’s Use of Cookies and NPII**  
Arth Salutions’s technology utilizes cookies in the delivery of advertisements to our Advertiser’s Prospects on our Partner’s websites across the internet. This form of marketing is called Retargeting; and it enhances the web surfing experience by showing advertisements to the Prospect that are of interest to them. When a Prospect visits one of Arth Salutions’s Advertiser’s websites, a Arth Salution pixel on that site sets a Arth Salution cookie on the hard drive of the Prospect. When that Prospect visits one of Arth Salutions’s Partners’ websites; our Partner’s website will identify the cookie on hard drive of the Prospect and recognize that they previously visited our Advertiser’s website. The Prospect will then be shown an advertisement from that Advertiser. In this instance, Arth Salutions will know that the Prospect first visited our Advertiser’s website, and then our Partner’s website. We will know the Prospect viewed the Ad on our Partner’s website, and whether or not the Prospect clicked on that Ad. This type information is what Arth Salution uses in reporting; and in no way can be used to identify who that Prospect is, or any other online activities of the Prospect outside of Arth Salutions’s Advertisers and Partner’s websites. 

The NPII data collected by Arth Salutions in the above outlined process of Retargeting will be kept by Arth Salutions indefinitely; and maintained and archived in our secured servers. This information is used strictly for reporting purposes and is not tied to personal information.

**How to Opt-Out of Arth Salutions’s Services**  
At any time you may Opt-Out of Arth Salutions’s services; however please note that by Opting-Out, you will not be able to take full advantage of Retargeted advertising. You are free to delete all cookies on your browser, or to have your browser notify you when a cookie is set – simply check your browser settings to do so. By deleting your cookies in this manner, you will disable Arth Salutions and it’s Partners to deliver ads that are targeted to your interests. You will have to clear your cookies each time you visit ArthSalutions.com or one of our Advertiser’s websites to ensure you are not receiving Retargeted advertisements.

**Another way to Opt-Out:**

Please [CLICK THIS LINK](http://www.arthsalutions.com/opt-out-confirmation/ "Opt Out") to Opt Out

When you Opt-Out of Arth Salutions’s services in this manner, a cookie will be set on your browser. Arth Salutions must maintain the cookie on your browser in order to recognize you as an Opted-Out visitor. You must Opt-Out again if you clear that cookie from your browser, use a different internet browser, or use a new computer to access the internet.

**Security**  
Arth Salutions takes the security of your information seriously, and we take measures to protect our data from unauthorized access, as well as unauthorized disclosure or destruction of data. Our data center provides the highest quality security for your data.

**Disclosure of Information to Third Parties**  
Personal Information  
Arth Salutions does not sell, trade, rent, or release your personal information to third parties in ways that are not disclosed in the privacy statement. If we were to ever do so, you will have the opportunity to Opt-Out beforehand.

**Transactional Information**  
Arth Salutions transactional information such as traffic patterns, sales, aggregate data regarding general shopping patterns, and other site information may be shared with vendors and other reputable third parties. This data will never contain any PII of Arth Salutions Users. For example, we might share statistics on how many customers purchased a specific product, but we will not specifically disclose who purchased the product.

**Legal Issues**  
Arth Salutions discloses personal information when required by law, judicial process, warrant, subpoena or in the good-faith belief that such action is necessary for the following:  
To conform to the edict of the law or comply with a legal process served on Arth Salutions or its Website. To protect and defend the property rights of Arth Salutions, the Arth Salutions Website, or that of Arth Salutions Users or to act under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of Arth Salutions Users, employees, or the general public.

**Other Sites’ Policies**  
Arth Salutions has no control over, nor does it bear any of the responsibility for the privacy policies and/or content of any sites or advertisers linked to or on ArthSalutions.com, or the cookies these sites might deposit on your hard drive.

**Your Consent & Contacting Us**  
Your Consent  
By visiting the Arth Salutions website, you consent to the collection, storage, and dissemination of personal data as described above. If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement, and other places we deem appropriate so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. We reserve the right to modify this privacy statement at any time, so please review it frequently.

**Effective Date**  
This policy was updated on June 08, 2012

**How To Contact Us**  
If you have any questions regarding our privacy policy please contact raaj@arthsalutions.com
